Hi everyone, welcome to another lecture
for CS230 deep learning. Today we're
going to talk about enhancing
large language model applications
and I I call this lecture beyond LLM.
Um it has a lot of newer content and uh
the idea behind this lecture is you we
started to learn about neurons and then
we learned about layers and then we
learned about deep neural networks and
then we learned a little bit about how
to structure projects in C3 and now
we're going one level beyond into what
would it look like if you were building
agentic AI systems at work in a startup
in a company. Um, and it's probably one
of the more practical lectures. Again,
the goal is not to build a product end
to end in the next hour or so, but
rather to tell you all the techniques
that AI engineers have cracked, figured
out, are exploring so that after the
class, you have sort of the breath of
view of different prompting techniques,
different agentic workflows, multi- aent
systems, eval when you want to dive
deeper, you have the baggage to dive
deeper and learn faster about it. Okay,
let's try to make it as interactive as
possible as usual. Um, when we look at
the agenda, the agenda is going to start
with the core idea behind challenges and
opportunities for augmenting LLMs. So,
we start from a base model. How do we
maximize the performance of that base
model? Um, then we'll dive deep into the
first line of optimization, which is
prompting methods, and we'll see a
variety of them. Then we'll go slightly
deeper. If we were to get our hands
under the hood and do some finetuning,
what would it look like? I'm not a fan
of fine-tuning, and I talk a lot about
that, but I'll explain why. I I try to
avoid fine-tuning as much as possible.
Um, and then we'll do a section four on
retrieval augmented generation or rag,
which you've probably heard of in the
news. Maybe some of you have played with
rags. We're going to sort of unpack what
a rag is and how it works and then the
different methods within
rags and then we'll talk about agentic
AI workflows. Um, I'll define it. Um
Andrew Ang is one of the call it first
ones to have called this trend a a
agentic AI workflows and so we look at
the definition that Andrew gives to
agentic workflows and then we start
seeing examples. The section six is very
practical. It's a case study where we
will think about an agentic workflow and
we'll and I ask you to measure um if the
agent actually works and we brainstorm
how we can measure if an agentic
workflow is working the way you want it
to work. There's plenty of methods
called eval that's um solve that
problem. uh and then we'll look briefly
at multi- aent workflow and then we can
have a a sort of open-ended discussion
where I'll share some thoughts on what's
next in AI. Um and I'm looking forward
to hearing from you all as well on that
one. Okay, so let's get started uh with
the problem of augmenting LLM. So
open-ended question for you. You are all
familiar with pre-trained models like
GPT3.5 Turbo or GPT40.
What's the limitation of using just a
base model? What are the typical issues
that might arise as you're using a
vanilla pre-trained model?
>> Yes.
>> Lacks some domain knowledge. You're
perfectly right. you know, you we we had
a group of students a few years ago was
not LLM related, but you know, they were
building a an autonomous uh farming uh
device or vehicle that had a camera
underneath taking pictures of crops to
determine if the crop is sick or not, if
it should be thrown away, like if it
should be if it should be used or not.
And and that data set is not a data set
you find out there. and the base model
or a pre-trained um computer vision
model would lack that knowledge of
course. What else?
Yes.
>> Okay. Maybe the you're saying so just to
re repeat for people online you're
saying the model might have been trained
on high quality data but the data in the
wild is actually not that high quality.
And in fact, yes, the distribution of
the real world might differ as we've
seen with GANs from the training set and
that might create an issue with
pre-trained models. Although pre-trained
LLMs are getting better at, you know,
handling all sorts of data inputs. Uh
yes,
>> current
>> lack what
>> lacks current information. Uh the LLM is
not up to date. And in fact, you're
right. Imagine you have to retrain from
scratch your LLM every couple of months.
Uh, one story that I found funny, um,
it's from probably three years ago or
maybe more, five years ago, where, um,
during his first presidency, President
Trump one day tweeted Kov Fe. You
remember that tweet or no, just Kof. And
it was probably a typo or it was in his
pocket, I don't know. But that word did
not exist. The LMS in fact that Twitter
was running at the time could not
recognize that word. And so uh the
recommener system sort of went wild
because suddenly everybody was making
fun of that tweet using the word kof and
the LM was so confused on you know what
does that mean where should we show it
to whom should we show it and is an
example of nowadays especially on social
media there's so many new trends and um
it's very hard to restrain an LLM to
match the new trend and understand the
new words out there. I mean, you know,
you often times hear Gen Z words like re
or mid or whatever. I don't know all of
them, but u you probably want to find a
way that can allow the LLM to understand
those trends without retraining the LLM
from scratch. Yeah. What else?
>> It's trained to have a breath of
knowledge and if you wanted to do
something specialized that might
>> Yeah. It might be trained on a breath of
knowledge but it might fail or not
perform adequately on a narrow task that
is very well defined. Think about
enterprise applications that yeah
enterprise application you need high
precision, high fidelity, low latency
and maybe the model is not great at that
specific thing. It might do fine but
just not good enough and you might want
to augment it in a certain way. Yeah.
[clears throat]
>> So it makes the model a lot heavier, a
lot slower.
>> So maybe it has a lot of broad domain
knowledge that might not be needed for
your application and so you're using a
massive heavy model when you actually
are only using 2% of the model
capability. You're perfectly right. You
might not need all of it. So you might
find ways to prune, quantize the model,
modify it. All of these are are are good
points. I'm going to add a few more as
well. Um, LLMs are very difficult to
control. Uh, your last point is actually
an example of that. You want to control
the LM to use a part of its knowledge,
but it's not. It's in fact getting
confused. Uh, we've seen that in
history. In 2016, Microsoft created a
notorious Twitter bot that learned from
users and it quickly became a racist
jerk. Microsoft ended up removing the
bot 16 hours after launching it. The
community was really fast at determining
that this was a racist bot. Um, and and
you know, you can empathize with
Microsoft in the sense that it is
actually hard to control an LLM. they
might have done a better job to qualify
before launching but it is really hard
to control an even more recently this is
a tweet from Samman last November um
where there was this debate between Elon
Musk and Samman on whose LLM is the
left-wing propaganda machine or the
right-wing propaganda machine and they
were hating on each other's LLMs but
that tells you at the end of the day
that even those two teams Grock and
OpenAI, which are probably the best
funded team with a lot of talent, are
not doing a great job at controlling
their LLMs, you know.
And from time to time, if you hang out
on X, you might see screenshots of users
interacting with LLMs and the LLM saying
something really controversial or or or
racist or, you know, something that
would not not be considered great
[laughter] by social standards, I guess.
And uh and that tells you that the model
is really hard to to control.
Um the second aspect of it is something
that you've mentioned earlier. LLMs may
underperform in your task. Um and that
might include specific knowledge gaps
such as medical diagnosis. If you're
doing medical diagnosis, you would
rather have an LLM that is specialized
for that and is great at it. And in
fact, something that we haven't
mentioned as a group has sources. So the
answer is sourced specifically. you have
a hard time believing something unless
you have the actual source of the
research that backs it up. Um,
inconsistencies in style and format. So,
imagine you're building a legal AI
agentic workflow. Uh, legal has a very
specific way to write and read uh where
every word counts. You know, if you're
negotiating a large contract, every word
on that contract might mean something
else when it comes to the court. And so
it's very important that you use an LLM
that is very good at it. The precision
matters. And then you know task specific
understanding such as doing a
classification on a niche field. Here I
pulled an example where you know let's
say a biotech product is trying to use
an LLM to categorize user reviews into
positive, neutral or negative. um you
know maybe for that company something
that's uh would be considered a negative
review typically is actually considered
a neutral review because the NPS of that
industry tends to be way lower than
other industries let's say um that's a
task specific understanding and the LLM
needs to be aligned to what the company
believes is the categorization that it
wants we will see an example of how to
solve that problem in a second and then
limited context handling. Um, a lot of
AI applications especially in the
enterprise have require data that has a
lot of context. Like just to give you a
simple example, knowledge management is
an important space that enterprises buy
a lot of knowledge management tool. When
you go on your drive and you have all
your documents, ideally you could have
an LLM running on top of that drive. You
can ask any question and it will read
immediately thousands of document and
answer what was our Q4 performance in
sales. Um it was X dollars. Uh it finds
it super quickly. In practice because
LLMs do not have a large enough context,
you cannot use a standalone vanilla
pre-trained LLM to solve that problem.
You will have to augment it.
Does that make sense?
>> [laughter]
>> Uh the other aspect around context
windows is they are in fact limited. If
you look at the context windows of the
models from the last 5 years um even the
best models today will range in context
window or number of tokens it can take
as input um somewhere in the hundreds of
thousands of tokens max. Just to give
you a sense 200,000 tokens is roughly
two books. Yeah. So that's how much you
can upload uh and it can read pretty
much and you can imagine that when
you're dealing with video understanding
or heavier data files that is of course
an issue.
So [snorts] you might have to chunk it,
you might have to embed it, you might
have to find other ways to get uh the
LLM to handle larger contexts.
Um the attention mechanism is also
powerful but a problematic because it
does not do a great job at attending in
very large contexts. There is actually
an interesting uh uh problem called
needle in a haststack. It's an AI
problem where or call it a benchmark
where um in order to test if your LLM is
good at attending at putting attention
on a very specific fact within a large
corpus, researchers might randomly
insert in a book one sentence that can
that that outlines a certain fact such
as Arun and Max are having coffee at
Blue Bottle in the middle of the Bible,
let's say or some very long text. Um and
then you ask the LLM um what were Arun
and Max having you know at Blue Bottle
and you see if it remembers that it was
coffee. It's actually a complex problem
not because the question is complex but
because you're asking the model to find
a fact within a very large corpus and
that's complicated.
So again this is a a limiting factor for
LLMs. We we'll talk about rag in a
second but I want to preview you know
the there is debates around whether rag
is the right long-term approach for AI
system. So as a as a high level idea a
rag is a mechanism if you will that
embeds documents that an LLM can
retrieve and then add as context to its
initial prompt and answer a question. It
has lots of application knowledge
management is an example. So imagine you
have your drive again but every document
is sort of compressed in representation
and the LLM has access to that lower
dimensional representation. Um the
debates that this tweet from Yu um
outlines is in theory if we have
infinite compute then rag is useless
because you can just read a massive
corpus immediately and answer your
question. But even in that case, latency
might be an issue. Imagine the time it
takes for an AI to read all your drive
every single time you ask a question. It
doesn't make sense. So, rag has other
advantages beyond even the accuracy. On
top of that, the sourcing matters as
well. So, it might rag allows you to
source. We'll talk we'll talk about all
that later. But there are there's always
this debate in the in the community
whether a certain method is actually
future proof because in practice as
compute power doubles every year let's
say some of the methods we're learning
right now might not be relevant 3 years
from now we don't know essentially
[snorts] um you know and and the analogy
that that he makes on on you know
context windows and why rag approaches
might be relevant even a long time from
Now um is search. You know when you
search on a search engine you still find
sources of information and in fact in
the background there is very
you know details traversal algorithms
that rank and find the specific links
that might be the the best to present
you. um versus if you had to read
imagine you had to read the entire web
every single time you're doing a search
query uh without being able to narrow to
certain portion of the space that might
again not be uh reasonable.
Okay, when we're thinking of improving
LLMs, the easiest way we think of it is
is two dimensions. One dimension is we
are going to improve the foundation
model itself. So for example, we move
from GPT uh 3.5 Turbo to GPT4 to GPT40
to GPT5. Each of that is supposed to
improve the base model. GPT5 is another
debate because it's sort of packaging
other models within itself. But you know
if you're thinking about 3.5 4 and 4,
that's really what it is. The
pre-trained model improves and so you
should see your uh performance improve
on your tasks. Um but the other
dimension is we can actually engineer
leverage the LLM in a way that makes it
better. So you can prompt simply GPT40.
You can
chain some prompts and improve the
prompt and it will improve the
performance. It's shown uh you can even
put a rag around it. You can put an
agentic workflow around it. You can even
put a multi- aent system around it. And
that is another dimension for you to
improve performance. So that's how I
want you to think about it. Which LLM
I'm using and then how can I maximize
the performance of that LLM.
This lecture is about the vertical axis.
Those are the methods that we will see
with it together.
Sounds good for the introduction. So
let's move to prompt engineering. Um I'm
going to start with an interesting study
just to motivate why prompt engineering
matters. Um there is a a study from uh
you know HPS, UPEN um uh as well as
Harvard Business School and and and
others also involve Wharton that took a
subset of BCG consultants, individual
contributors, split them into three
groups. One group had no access to AI.
One group had access to I think it was
GPT 4. Um and then one group had access
to the LLM but also a training on how to
prompt better. Um and then they observed
the performance of these consultants
across a wide variety of tasks. There's
a few things that they noticed that I
thought was interesting. One is
something they call the JAG frontier. um
meaning that certain tasks that
consultants are doing fall beyond the
jack frontier. Meaning AI is uh is not
good enough. It's not it's not improving
human performance. In fact, it's
actually making it worse. Um and some
tasks are within the frontier, meaning
that uh AI is actually significantly
improving the performance, the speed,
the quality of the consultant. Um many
tasks fail within and many tasks fail
without and they shared their um
insights but the TLDDR is there is a
frontier within which AI is absolutely
helping and one where they call out this
behavior of falling asleep at the wheel
where people relied on AI on a task that
was beyond the frontier and in fact it
ended up going worst because the human
was not reviewing the outputs carefully
enough. Um
they did note that the the group that
was trained was uh the best uh better
than the group that was not trained on
prompt engineering which also motivates
why this lecture matters. Um so that
you're you're you're within that group
afterwards. One other insights um were
the centurs and the cyborgs. They
noticed that consultants had the
tendency to work with AI in one of two
ways and you might yourself find be part
of one of these groups. The centaurs are
mythical creatures that are half human,
half
I think half
like what? Horses. Yeah, horses. Half
horses, half something. Um, and those
were individuals that would divide and
delegate. They might give a pretty big
task to the AI. So imagine you're
working on a PowerPoint, which
consultants are known to do. um you
might actually write a very long prompt
on how you wanted to do your PowerPoint
and then let it work for some time and
then come back and it's done when others
would act as cyborgs. Cyborgs are fully
blended bionic human robots, a human
robot and robot augmented with robotic
parts. Uh and those individuals would
not delegate fully a task. They would
actually work super quickly with the
model and like back and forth. I find
that a lot of students are actually more
working like cyborgs than centaurs. But
while maybe in the enterprise when
you're trying to automate a workflow,
you're thinking more like a centur.
Yeah, that's just something good to keep
in mind. Also, a lot of companies would
tell you, oh, we're hiring prompt
engineers, etc. It's a curer. I I don't
buy that. I think it's just a skill that
everybody should have. uh you're not
going to make a career out of prompt
engineering, but you're probably going
to use it as a very powerful skill in
your career.
Um so let's talk about basic prompt
design principles. I'm giving you a very
simple prompt here. Summarize this
document and then the document is
uploaded alongside it. And the model has
not um much context around you know what
should be the summary, how long should
be read the summary, what should it talk
about. etc. You can actually improve
these prompts um by by doing you know
something like summarize this 10page
scientific paper on renewable energy in
five bullet points focusing on key
findings and implications for policy
makers. That's already better, right?
You're sharing the audience and it's
going to tailor it to the audience.
You're saying that you want five bullet
points and you want focus only on key
findings. You know, that's a better
prompt, you would argue. Um, how could
you even make this prompt better? What
are other techniques that you've heard
of or tried yourself that could make
this oneshot prompt better?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Right. Right. Example. So, say uh
you mean here is an example of a great
summary. Yeah, you're right. That's a
good idea.
to be like someone act like you are
>> very popular technique act like a
renewable energy expert giving a
conference at Davos let's say yeah
that's great someone
>> sounds
like you're really good at it like
>> you are the best in the world at this
explain [laughter] yeah actually I mean
these things work it's funny but uh it
does work to to say act like xyz it's a
very popular prompt template But we
we'll see a few examples. What else
could you do?
>> Yes.
>> I personally like to say critique your
own project.
>> Okay.
>> Critique your own project. So you're
using reflection. So you might actually
do one output and then ask it to
critique it and then give it back. Yeah,
we'll see that. That's a great one.
That's that's the one that probably
works best within those typically, but
we we'll see some examples. What else?
Yeah.
>> Breaks.
>> Okay. break the task down into steps. Do
you know how that is called?
>> No.
>> Okay. Chain of thoughts. So, um this is
actually a popular method that's been
shown in in research that it improves.
You could actually give a clear
instruction and also encourage the model
to think step by step. Approach the task
step by step and do not skip any step.
And then you give it some steps such as
step one identify the three most
important findings. Step two, explain
how key each finding impact renewable
energy policy. Step three, write the
five bullet summary with each point
addressing a finding um etc. So, chain
of thoughts, I linked the paper from
2023 uh that popularized chain of
thoughts. Chain of thoughts is very very
popular right now, especially in AI
startups that are trying to control
their elements.
Okay, [snorts] to go back to your
examples about act like XYZ,
I what I like to do, Andrew also talks
about that uh is to look at other
people's prompts and in fact in online
you have a lot of prompt repositories
for free on GitHub. In fact, I I linked
the awesome prompt template repo on
GitHub where you have so many examples
of great prompt that engineers have
built. They said it works great for us
and they published it online. And a lot
of them starts with act as you know act
as a Linux terminal, act [laughter] as
an English translator, act like um a
position interviewer, etc.
The advantage of a prompt template is
that you can actually put it in your
code and scale it for many user
requests. So let me give you an example
from worker. um you know where Cara
evaluates skills some of you have taken
the assessments already and um tries to
personalize it to the user um and in
fact if you actually read in an HR
system in an enterprise in the HR system
you might have Jane is a product manager
level three and she is uh in the US and
her preferred language is English and
actually that metadata can be inserted
in a prompt template that we personalize
for Jane and similarly for Joe whose
favorite language is preferred language
is Spanish. It will it will tailor it to
Joe and that's called the prompt
template.
>> Yeah.
>> Foundation models they don't use
something you have to.
>> So uh the question is do the foundation
models use a prompt templates or do you
have to integrate it yourself? So the
foundation models probably use a system
prompt that you don't see like when
actually you type on chatgpt it is
possible it's not public that openai
behind the scene has like act like a
very helpful assistant for this user and
by the way here is your memories about
your the user that we kept in a database
you can actually check your memories and
then your prompt goes under and then the
generation starts. So probably they're
using something like that, but it
doesn't mean you can't um add one
yourself. So in fact, if you if you
think about a prompt template for for
the work here example I was showing,
maybe it starts when you call OpenAI by
act like a head assistant and then
underneath it's like act like a great uh
AI mentor that helps people in their
career and OpenAI's Chrome template also
has follow the instruction from the
creator or something like that, you
know, it's possible. Yeah.
U questions about prompt templates.
Again, I would encourage you to go and
read examples of prompts. Some of them
are quite thoughtful.
Um let's talk about zero shot versus few
shot prompting. It came up earlier.
Here's an example. Again, going back to
the categorization of product reviews.
Let's say that we're working on a task
where the prompt is classify the tone of
this sentence as positive, negative, or
neutral. and the the and then you paste
the review which is the product is fine
but I was expecting more.
If I were to survey the room I would bet
that some of you would say it's
negative, some of you would say it's
neutral because you actually have a
first part that is relatively
positive. It's fine and then the second
part I was expecting more which is
relatively negative. So where do you
land? This can be a subjective question
and maybe in one industry this would be
considered amazing and another one it
would be considered really bad because
people are used to really flourishing
reviews. And so the way you can actually
align the model to your task is by
converting that zero shot prompt. Zero
shot refers to the fact that it's not
beginning given any example uh into a
few short prompts where the model is
given in the prompt a set of examples to
align it to what you want it to do. So
the example here is you you again you
paste the same prompt as before with the
user review and then you add here are
examples of tone classifications. This
exceeded my expectation completely.
Positive. It's okay but I wish it had
more features. Negative. The service was
adequate. Neither good nor bad. Uh
neutral. Now classify the tone of this
sentence um you know after you've heard
about these things. And the model then
says negative. And the reason it says
negative of course is likely um because
of the second example which was it's
okay but I wish it had more features
which we told the model that was
negative because the model saw that it's
aligned now with your expectations.
Fshot prompts are very popular. Um, and
in fact, for AI startups that are
slightly more sophisticated, you might
see them uh keep a prompt up to date,
whenever the a user says something and
they might have a human label it and
then add it as a few shots in the
relevant prompt in their codebase. Um,
you can think of that as almost building
a data set, but instead of actually
building a separate data set like we've
seen with supervised fine-tuning and
then train fine-tuning the model on it,
you're just putting it directly in the
prompt. And turns out it's probably
faster to do that if you want to
experiment quickly because you don't
touch the model parameters. You just
update your prompts. And you know if
it's text examples, you can actually you
know concatenate so many examples uh in
a single prompt. At some point it will
be too long and you will not have the
necessary context window. But it's a
pretty strong approach that is quick to
align an LM.
Okay. Yes.
>> Research on how long can be until it
starts with
>> So question was is there any research on
how long the prompt can be before the
model essentially loses itself or
doesn't follow instructions anymore?
There is uh the problem is that research
is outdated every few months uh because
models get better. Um and so I I don't
know where the state-of-the-art is. You
can probably find it online on
benchmarks on like we see that I I I
give an example uh on the worker product
you have um a voice conversation for
some of you that have tried it where you
you're ask explain what is a prompt and
then you explain and then there's a
scoring algorithm in behind we know that
after eight turns the model loses itself
after eight turns because you always
paste the previous user response it just
starts going wild and so the techniques
we use in the background is we actually
create chapters of the conversation.
Maybe one chapter is the first aid
prompt and then you actually start over
from another prompt. You you can
summarize the first part of the
conversation, insert the summary and
then keep going. You know, those are
engineering hacks that engineers might
have figured out in the background.
Yeah. Because yeah, eight turns makes a
prompt quite long actually.
[snorts] Uh let's move on to chaining.
uh chaining is the most popular
technique out of everything we've seen
so far in uh uh in prompt engineering.
Uh it's not chain of thought. So chain
of thought we've seen is think step by
step, step one, step two, step three, do
not skip any step. This is different.
This is chaining complex prompt to
improve performance. And this is what it
looks like. Um, you take a singlestep
prompt such as read this customer review
and write a professional response that
acknowledges their concern, explains the
issue, offers a resolution, and then you
paste the customer review, which is, I
ordered a laptop, it arrived 3 days
late, the packaging was damaged, very
disappointing. I need it that urgently
for work. And then the output is an
email that is immediately given to you
by the LLM after it reads the prompt.
Um, so this might work, but it might be
hard to control, you know, cuz think
about it. There's multiple steps that
you have listed and everything is
embedded in the same prompt. And if you
wanted to debug step by step and know
which step is weaker, you couldn't. You
would have everything mixed together. So
one advantage of chaining is you know
you would you would separate the prompts
so that you can debug them separately
and it will also lead to um an easier
manner to improve your workflow. Um
let's say a first prompt is extract the
key issues. Identify the key concerns
mentioned in this customer review. Paste
a customer review. Second prompt using
these issues. So you paste back the
issues. Draft an outline for a
professional response that acknowledges
concerns, explains possible reasons, and
offer a resolution.
So, this is not, you know, prompt number
three, write the full response. So,
using the outline, um, write the
professional response
and then you get your final output.
So, in theory, you can't tell me, oh,
the second approach is better than the
first one at first. But what you can
notice is that we can actually test
those three prompts separately from each
other and determine if we will get the
most gains out of uh engineering the
first prompt, optimizing it or the
second one or the third one. We now have
three prompts that are independent from
each other. And you know maybe if uh the
outline was better um the performance of
uh the email the email how much it will
the open rate will be or the user
satisfaction on the response will
actually get higher you know and so
chaining
improves performance but most
importantly helps you control your
workflow and debug it more seamlessly.
>> Yes.
So [snorts] if we know that the three
pump independently work very well, if we
combine them into one pump and we
highlight that stepbystep thinking
process, do we does on average we get
the same policy output or we still have
to do that break down?
>> So let me try to rephrase you say let's
say we look at the first prompt which
has uh all three task built in that
prompt. Um what what exactly do you
mean? You mean like if we evaluate the
output and we measure some user insight,
satisfaction, etc. Um why don't we just
modify that prompt and essentially see
how it improves user satisfaction?
>> Yeah, instead process.
>> I see. See, why do we need the three
steps?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I mean, think about it. The
intermediate output is what you want to
see. Like if I'm debugging the first um
approach, uh the way I would do it is I
would capture user insights. Like here's
the email, how good was the response?
Thumbs up, thumbs down. Um was your
issue issue resolved? Uh thumbs up,
thumbs down. Those would tell me how
good is my prompt? And I can engineer
that prompt, optimize it, and I would
probably drive some gains. Um but I will
not be able easily to trace back to what
the problem was. While in the second
approach, not only I can use the end to
end metrics to improve my process, I can
also use the intermediate steps. For
example, if I look at prompt two and I
look at the outline and I see the
outline is actually meh, it's not great,
then I think I can get a lot of gains
out of the outline. Um, or the outline
is actually really good, but the last
prompt doesn't do a good job at
translating it into an email. So the
outline is exactly what I want the the
LLM to do, but the the translation in a
customerf facing email is not good. In
fact, it doesn't follow our vocabulary
internally.
Then I know the third prompt is where I
would get the most gains.
So that that's what it allows me to do.
Have intermediate steps to review.
>> Yeah.
>> Are there any lat?
>> We'll talk about it. Are there any
latency concerns? Yes. um in certain
applications um you don't want to use a
chain or you don't want to use a long
chain because it adds latency.
We'll talk about that later. Good point.
So practically this is what uh chaining
complex prompts look like. You have your
first prompt with your first task. It
outputs the output is is pasted in the
second prompt with the second task being
defined. The output is then pasted into
the third prompt with the third task
being defined and so on. That's what it
looks like in practice.
Super. U
we'll talk more later about testing your
prompts, but there are methods now to do
it and we'll we'll see later in this
lecture with our case study how uh we
can test our prompts. Uh but here is an
example of how you you might do it. Um
you you might have a a summarization
workflow, you know, prompt um that is
the baseline. It's a single uh prompt.
You might have a refined summarization
which is a modified prompt of this or a
workflow with a chain, you know. Um, and
then you have your test case, which is
the input that you want to summarize,
let's say, and then you have the
generated output, and you can have
humans go and rate these outputs. And
you would notice uh that the baseline is
better or worse than the refined prompt.
Of course, this manual approach takes
time. Um, but it's a good way to start
and usually the advice is get hands-on
at the beginning because you would
quickly notice some issues and it will
give you better intuition on what tweaks
can lead to better performance. However,
if you wanted to scale that system
across many products, many parts of your
codebase, uh you might want to find a
way to do that automatically without
asking humans to review and grade
summaries, right? Um, one approach is
to, um, use, you know, platforms like at
Portera, we, our team uses a platform
called Prompt Fu that allows you to
actually automate part of this testing.
Um, in a nutshell, what it does is it
can allow you to run the same prompt
with five different LLMs immediately,
put everything in a table that makes it
super easy for a human to grade, let's
say. Or alternatively, it might allow
you to define define LLM judges.
LLM judges can come in different
flavors. For example, I can have an LLM
judge that does a pair-wise comparison.
So, what the LLM is asked to do is here
are two summaries. Just tell me which
one is better than the other one. Um,
that's what the LLM does. And that can
be used as a proxy for how good the
summarization baseline versus the
refined version is. Another way to do an
LLMA judge is if you do it for a single
answer grading. So here's a summary,
grade it from one to five, you know, and
then you can go even deeper and do a a
reference guided pair wise comparison or
you add also a rubric. You say a five is
when a summary is below 100 characters.
I'm just making up below 100 characters
mentions at least three key points that
are distinct and starts with a first
sentence that displays the overview and
then goes into the detail. That's a
great summary number five out of five.
Zero is the LLM failed to summarize and
actually was very verbose let's say and
so you put a rubric behind it and you
have an LLM as just finding the rubric.
Of course you can now pair different
techniques. You can do a few shot for
the rubric. You can actually give
examples of a five out of fives, four
out of fours, three out of threes
because now you know multiple
techniques. Okay, [clears throat]
does that make sense?
Yeah. Okay. So that was the second
section on prompt engineering uh or the
first line of optimization. Now, let's
say you've exhausted all your chances
for prompt engineering and you're
thinking about actually touching the
model, modifying its weights or
fine-tuning it. In other words, um I was
telling you I'm not a a fan of
fine-tuning. There's a few reasons why.
Um one, it requires substantial label
data typically to fine-tune. Although
now there are approaches that are
getting better at fine-tuning that look
more like few shot prompting actually
than fine-tuning. It's sort of merging
uh although one modifies the weight, the
other doesn't modify the weights. Um
fine-tune models may also overfeed to
specific data. We're going to see a
funny example actually. Um losing uh
their general purpose utility. So you
might fine-tune a model and actually
when someone asks a pretty generic
question, it doesn't do well anymore.
You know, it might do well on your task.
So it might be relevant or not. And then
it's it's time and cost intensive.
That's my main problem. And you know, at
at work here, we don't we don't we steer
away from fine-tuning as much as
possible. Uh because by the time you're
done fine-tuning your model, the next
model is out and it's actually beating
your fine tuned version of the previous
model. So I would steer away from
fine-tuning as much as you can. The
advantage of the prompt engineering
methods we've seen is you can put the
next best pre-trained model directly in
your code. It will update everything
immediately. Fine-tuning doesn't work
like that.
[laughter] There are advantages though
where it still makes sense. if the task
requires repeated high precision output
such as legal scientific explanation and
if the general purpose LLM struggles
with domain specific language. So, uh,
let's look at a quick example together,
um, which is an example, uh, from Ross
Lazerovitz, um, I think it was a couple
of years ago, September 23, where, um,
uh, Ross tried to do Slack finetuning.
So, he looked at a lot of Slack messages
within his company and he was like, I'm
going to fine-tune a model that speaks
like us or operates like us because this
is how we work, right? this is the data
that represents how people work at the
company. Um and so it he actually went
ahead and fine-tuned the model. Um gave
it a prompt like hey write a you know he
was delegating to the model write a
500word blog post on prompt engineering
and the model responded I shall work on
that in the morning. Um
and and then he tries to push the model
a little further and say it's morning
now. Um, and the model said, "I'm
writing right now. It's 6:30 a.m. here.
Uh, write it now." Okay, please.
[laughter]
Okay, I shall write it now. I actually
don't know what you would like me to say
about prompt engineering. I can only
describe the process. The only thing
that comes to mind for a headline is how
do we build prompt? You know, it's kind
of a funny example for fine-tuning
because it's true that it went wrong.
like he was supposed to think like I
want the model to speak like us at work
and it ended up acting like people and
not actually following instructions.
So one example why I would steer away
from fine tuning.
Super
uh
let's talk about rags. Um rags is
important. It's important to know out
there and at least having the basics.
It's a very common interview question by
the way. If you go interview for a job,
they might ask you to explain in a
nutshell to a 5-year-old what is a rag
and hopefully after that you'll be able
to do it. Um, so, uh, we've seen some of
the challenges with standalone LLMs.
Those challenges include the context
window being small, the fact that it's
hard to remember details within a large
context window, um, knowledge gaps, you
know, uh, cutoff dates you mentioned
earlier. The model might be trained up
to a date and then it cannot follow the
trends or be up to date. Hallucinations
there are some fields think about
medical diagnosis where hallucination
are very costly. You can't afford a
hallucination. You know even in
education imagine deploying a model for
the US youth education and it
hallucinates and it teaches millions of
people something completely wrong. It's
a problem. Um and then lack of sources.
Uh a lot of fields love sources.
research fields love sources. Education
loves sources. Legal loves sources as
well. And so um the pre-trained LLM
doesn't do a good job to source. And in
fact, if you if you have tried to find
sources on a plain LLM, it actually
hallucinates a lot. It makes up research
papers. It just lists like completely
fake stuff. Um so how do we solve that?
Um with a rag. Rag integrates with
external knowledge sources, databases,
documents, APIs.
It ensures that answers are more
accurate, upto-date and grounded because
you can actually update your document.
Your your drive is always up to date. I
mean ideally you're always pushing new
documents to it. And when you query what
is our Q4 performance in sales,
hopefully there is the last board deck
in uh the drive and it can read the last
board deck. Yeah. [snorts] Um and more
developer control. We'll see why um rags
allow for targeted customization without
actually requiring the retraining of the
model. In fact, you don't touch the
model with rags. It's really a technique
that is put on top of the model. So to
see an example of a a rag, this is a
question answering
application where we're in the medical
field and a user is asking uh a query.
What are the side effects of drug X?
This is an important question. You can't
hallucinate. You need to source. You
need to be up to date. Maybe there is a
new
update to that drug that is now in the
database and you need to read that. So
you have to like a rag is a great
example of what you would want to use
here. The the way it works is you have
your knowledge base of a bunch of
documents. Um what you do is you use an
embedding to embed those documents into
lower dimensional representations.
So for example if the document is a PDF
a long PDF uh you might you know read
the PDF understand it and then embed it.
We've seen plenty of embedding
approaches together. triplet loss etc.
you remember. So imagine one of them
here for LLMs is embedding those
documents into lower representation.
If the representation is too small, you
will lose information. If it's too big,
you will add latency, right? It's a
trade-off. Um
you will store typically those
representation into a database um called
a vector database. There's a lot of
vector database providers as out there.
Um you know I I I think I've listed a
couple that are very common. No I
haven't listed but I can I can share
afterwards. Um the vector database is
essentially storing those vector in a
very efficient manner allowing the fast
retrieval
with a certain distance metric. So um
what you do is you also embed usually
with the same algorithm the user prompts
and you run a retrieval process which is
essentially saying um based on the
embedding from the user query and the
vector database find the relevant
documents based on the distance between
those embeddings.
Once you found the relevant documents,
you pull them and then you add them to
the user query with a system prompt or a
prompt template on top. So the prompt
template can be um answer user query
based on list of documents.
If answer not in the document say I
don't know. That's your prompt templates
where the user query is pasted. the
documents are pasted and then your
output um should be what you want
because it's now grounded in the
document. You can also add to this
prompt templates tell me the exact page,
chapter line of the document that was
relevant and in fact link it as well
just to be more precise.
Any question on rags? There's a simple
vanilla rag.
Yeah. Yes. document embeddings still
retain information about what's down on
what page and what paragraph?
>> Question is, do the document embeddings
still retain the information of the
location of the information within that
document, especially in big documents?
Um, great question. We'll get to it in a
in a second because you're right that
the vanilla rag might not do a good job
with very large documents. So let's say
uh you know when you open a medication
box and you have this gigantic uh white
paper with all the information and it's
very long uh maybe a vanilla rag would
not cut it. So what people have figured
out is a bunch of techniques to improve
rags and in fact chunking is a great
technique that is very popular. So you
might actually store in the vector
database the embedding of the full
document and on top of that you will
also store a chapter level uh vector you
know and when you retrieve you retrieve
the document you retrieve the chapter
and that allows you to be more precise
with the sourcing. It's one example.
Um another technique that's popular is
hide um hypothetical document embeddings
where a group of researchers
um published a paper showing that when
you get your user query one of the main
problem is the user query actually does
not look like your documents. For
example, the user query might be what
are the side effect of drug X when
actually in the document in the vector
database the vectors represents very
long documents. So how do you guarantee
that the vector embedding is going to be
close to the document embedding? What
they do is they use the user query to
generate a fake hallucinated document.
They embed that document and then they
compare to the vector in the vector
database. Does that make sense? So for
example, the user says, "What is the
side effect of drug X?" There's a prompt
that this is given to another prompt
that says, "Based on this user query,
generate a five-page report answering
the user query." It generates
potentially a completely fake um u
answer. You embed that and it will be
closer to the document that you're
looking for likely. Yeah,
it's one example of a of a rag approach.
Again, the purpose of this lecture is
not to go through all these three and
explain you every single methods that
has been discovered for rags, but I just
wanted to show you how much research has
been done between 2020 and 2025 in rags
and how many branches of research you
you now have that you can uh learn from.
The survey paper is linked in the
slides, by the way, and I'll share them
after the lecture.
>> [laughter]
>> Super.
So, uh, we've made some progress.
Hopefully now you feel like if you were
to start an LLM application, you know
how to do better prompts, you know how
to do chains, you know how to do
fine-tuning, uh you also know how to do
retrieval and you have the baggage of
techniques that you can go and read and
find the codebase, pull the code, vi
code it, but you have the breath. Now
u the next set of uh topics we're going
to see is around uh the question of how
could we extend the capabilities of LLM
from performing single tasks and hands
with external knowledge to handling
multi-step autonomous workflows. Yeah.
And this is where we get into proper
agent AI.
So let's talk about agent TKI workflows
towards autonomous and specialized
systems.
Then we'll talk about evals. Then we'll
see multi- aent systems. And we'll end
with a with a little
thoughts on what's next in AI.
So um Andrew Wang actually
coined the term agentic AI workflows. Um
and his reason was that a lot of
companies use uh let's say agents,
agents, agents everywhere. Agents
everywhere.
If you go and work at these companies,
you would notice that they mean very
different things by agent. Some people
actually have a prompt and they call it
an agent. You know, other people they
have a very complex multi- aent system.
They call it an agent. And so calling
everything an agent doesn't do it
justice. So Andrew says, "Let's call it
agentic workflows because in practice
it's a bunch of prompts with tools with
additional resources, API calls that
ultimately are put in a workflow and you
can call that workflow agentic. So it's
all about the multi-step process
um to complete the task.
Also calling it agentic workflow allows
us to not mix it up with what I called
agent the the last lecture with
reinforcement learning because in RL
agent has a very specific definition
interacts with an environment passes
from one state to the other has a reward
and an observation. You remember that
chart right?
So um here's an example of how we move
from a one-step prompt to a a multi-step
agentic workflow. Let's say a user
queries a a
a product, what is your refund policy on
a chatbot? Um, and the response using a
rag says refunds are available within 30
days of purchase. And maybe the rag can
even look linked to the policy document.
That's what we learned so far. Um,
instead an agenting workflow can
function like this. The user says, "Can
I get a refund for my order?" And the
response via the agentic workflow is the
agent retrieves the refund policy using
a rag. The agent then follows up with
the users and says can you provide your
order number? Um then the agent queries
an API to check the order details and
finally it comes back to the user and
confirms your order qualifies for a
refund. The amount will be processed in
3 to five business days. This is much
more thoughtful than the first version
which is sort of vanilla, right?
So that's what we're going to talk about
in the next couple of slides is how do
we get from the first one to the second
one.
Uh there are plenty of specialized
agentic workflows online. You know,
you've heard and if you hang out in SF,
you probably see a bunch of billboards,
you know, AI software engineer, AI
skills mentor you've interacted with in
the class to worker, AISDR, AI lawyers,
AI,
you know, specialized cloud engineer.
You know, it would be a stretch to say
that everything works, but there's work
being done towards that. Yeah,
I'm not personally a fan of putting a
face behind those things. I think it's
gimmicky and I think in a few years from
now actually very few products will have
a human face behind it. Uh but might be
a marketing tactic from some startups.
It's more scary than it is engaging
frankly. Um okay, I want to talk about
the pirating shift. Uh that's especially
useful. Let's say you're a software
engineer or you're planning to be a
software engineer because software
engineering as a discipline is sort of
shifting or at least the best engineers
I've worked with are able to move from a
deterministic mindset to a fuzzy mindset
and balance between the two whenever
they need to get something done. So
here's the paring shift between
traditional software and agent TKI
software. The first one is uh the way
you handle data. Traditional software
deals with structured data. You have
JSONs, you have databases. They're
pasted in a very structured manner in a
data engineering pipeline and then
they're used to be displayed on a
certain interface. The user might feel
fill a form that is then retrieved and
pasted in the database. All of that
historically has been structured data.
Now more and more companies are handling
uh free form text, images um and and all
of that requires dynamic interpretation
um uh to transform an input into an
output. Um the software itself used to
be deterministic. Now you have a lot of
software that is fuzzy and fuzzy
software creates so many issues. I mean,
imagine if you let your user ask
anything on your website.
The chances that it breaks is
tremendous. The chances that you're
attacked is tremendous. The chances,
it's really, really complicated. It's
more complicated than people make it
seem uh on Twitter. [snorts] Um, fuzzy
engineering is truly hard. Yeah, you
might get hate as a company because one
user did something that you authorized
them to do that ended up breaking the
database and ended up, you know, we've
seen that with many companies in the
last couple of years. So, it takes a
very specialized engineering mindset to
do fuzzy engineering, but also know when
you need to be deterministic.
Um, the other thing I call is with
agentic AI software, um, you you you
sort of want to think about your
software as like your manager. So you're
familiar with the monolith or or you
know microservices approaches in
software you know where you structure
your software in different you know
boxes that can talk to each other and it
allows teams to debug one section at a
time you know now the equivalent with
agentic AI is you think as a manager. So
you think okay if I was to delegate my
product to be done by a group of humans
what would be those roles? Would I have
a graphic designer that then you know
puts together a chart and then sends it
to a marketing manager that converts it
into a nice blog post that then gives it
to the performance marketing expert that
then publishes the work the blog post
and then optimizes and AB tests then to
a data scientist that analyzes the data
and then puts hypothesis and validates
them or invalidates them. That's how you
would typically think if you're building
an agency AI software
when actually the equivalent of that in
traditional software might be completely
different. It might be we have a data
engineer box right here that handles all
our data engineering. And then here we
have the UIUX stuff. Everything UIUIX
related goes here. And you know
companies might structure it in very
different ways. And here's the business
logic that we want to care about. And
there's five engineers working on the
business logic. let's say
okay [snorts and laughter] uh testing
and debugging is also very different um
and we'll talk about it in the next
section.
uh the other thing that uh I feel
matters is with AI in engineering the
cost of experimentation is going down
drastically and so people I feel should
be more comfortable throwing away code
you know it's it's like in traditional
software engineering you probably don't
throw away code a ton you you build a
code and it's solid and it's bulletproof
and then you you update it over time
when we've seen AI companies be more
comfortable throwing away codes. Yeah.
Which has advantages in terms of the
speed at which you move but also
disadvantages in terms of the quality of
your software that it can break more.
No.
Okay. So anyway, just wanted to do an
aparte on the the parading shift from
deterministic to fuzzy engineering.
Um,
oh, and actually I can give you an
example from uh from worker that we
learned uh probably over the last 12
months is like if you if you've used
worker you might have seen that the
interface has um asks you sometimes
multiple choice questions and sometimes
it asks you multiple select and
sometimes it asks you drag and drop
ordering matching whatever right those
are example of deterministic item types
meaning you answer the question on a
multiple le choice there's one correct
answer it's fully deterministic. On the
other hand you sometimes have voice
questions uh where you go through a role
play or you have voice plus coding
questions where your code is being read
by the interface or whatever. Those are
fuzzy, meaning the scoring algorithm
might actually make mistakes and those
mistakes might be costly. And so
companies have to figure out a human in
the loop system, which you might have
seen with the appeal feature at the end.
So at the end of the assessment, you
have an appeal feature where it allows
you to say, I want to appeal the agent
because I want to challenge what the
agent said on my answer because I
thought I was better than what the agent
thought. And then you bring a human in
the loop that then can fix the agent,
can tell the agent, actually you were
too harsh on the answer of this person.
Um, and you know, that's an example of a
fuzzy engineered system that then adds a
human in the loop to make it more
aligned. And so if you're building a
company, I would encourage you to think
about what can I get done with
determinism and let's get that done. And
then the fuzzy stuff, I want to do fuzzy
because it allows more interaction. It
allows more back and forth, but I need
to put guard rails around it. And how am
I going to design those guard rails
pretty much? All right,
here's another example uh from
enterprise workflows um which are likely
to change due to agent AI. Um this is a
paper from McKenzie uh I believe from
last year where they looked at a
financial institution and they said that
you know we observe that they often
spend one to four weeks to create a
credit risk memo and here is the
process. A relationship manager
um gathers data from 15 and more than 15
sources on the borrower loan type other
factors. Then the relationship manager
and the credit analyst collaboratively
analyze that data from these sources.
Then the credit analyst typically spends
you know 20 more 20 hours or more
writing a memo and then goes back to the
relationship manager. They give feedback
and then they go through this loop again
and again and uh it takes a long time to
get a credit memo out and then then run
a a research study where they changed
the process. They said Genai agents
could actually cut time um by 20 to 60%
on credit risk memos and the process has
changed to the relationship manager
directly work with the genai agent
system provides relevant materials that
needs to produce the memo. The agent
subsizes the project into tasks that are
assigned to specialist agents gathers
and analyzes the data from multiple
sources. Drafts a memo. Then the
relationship manager and the credit
analyst sit down together, review the
memo, give feedback to the agent, and
within, you know, 20 to 60% less time
are done. And so this is an example
where you're actually not changing the
human stakeholders, you're just changing
the process and adding genai to uh
reduce the time it takes to get a credit
memo out. It turns out that um imagine
you're an enterprise and you have you
know 100,000 employees and there's a lot
of enterprises with 100,000 employees
out there. Uh you are currently under
crisis in terms of redesigning your
workflows. You you are you know it turns
out that if you actually pull the job
descriptions from the HR system and you
interpret them you also pull the
business process workflows that you have
encoded in your drive. you actually can
find gains in multiple places and uh in
the next few years you're probably going
to see workflows being more optimized to
add genai. Um even if that happens the
hardest part is changing people. What we
know this is this is great in theory but
now let's try to fit that second
workflow for 10,000 credit risk analysts
and relationship managers. My guess is
it will take years. It will take 10 20
years to get to this being actually done
at scale within an organization because
change is so hard you know so hard to
rewire business workflows job
descriptions incentivize people to do
different and be different and train
them and so so you know this is what the
world is going towards but it's going to
take a long time I think
um okay then I want to talk about how
the agent actually works and What are
the core core components of an agent? U
imagine um a travel booking AI agent.
That's an easy example you've all
thought about. I still haven't been able
to get an agent to book a trip for me or
or I was scared because it was going to
book a very expensive or long trip. But
in theory um uh you you can you can have
a travel booking agent that has prompts.
So the prompts we've seen we know the
methods to optimize those prompts. That
travel agent also has a content
management context management system
which is essentially the memory of what
it knows about the user. That context
management system might include a core
memory or working memory and an archival
memory. Okay. What the difference is um
within memory um is not every memory
needs to be fast to access. Like think
about it. you you're born on a product
and the first question is hi what's your
name and I say my name is Keon that's
probably going to sit in the working
memory because the agent every time he's
going to talk to me is going to want to
use my name right but then maybe the
second question is Keon what's your
birthday and I give it my birthday does
it need my birthday every day probably
not so it's probably going to park it on
the long-term memory or the archival
memory and those memories are slower to
access they're farther down the stack
and you know that structure allows agent
to determine what's the working memory
and what's the long-term memory you know
and that makes it easier for the agent
to retrieve super fast cuz think about
it when you interact with GPT you feel
that it's very personal at times right
you feel like it understands you um
imagine every time you call it it has to
read the memories right and that can be
costly it's like a very it's a very
burdensome cost because it happens every
time you you talk to it So you want to
be highly optimized with the working
memory. You know, if it takes 3 seconds
to look in the memory, every time you're
going to talk to your LLM, it's going to
take 3 seconds, which you don't want. So
anyway, and then you have the tools. The
tools can include uh APIs like a flight
search API, hotel booking API, car
rental API, weather API, and then the
payment processing API. And typically,
you would want to tell your agent how
that API works. It turns out that agents
or LLMs I should say are very good at
reading API documentation. So you give
it the API documentation and it reads
the JSON and it reads what does a get
request look like and this is the format
that I need to push and then it pushes
it in that format let's say and then it
retrieves something.
Does that make sense? Those different
components
you know entropic also talks about
resources. resources is data that is
sitting somewhere that you might let
your agent read. For example, if you're
building your startups, you have a CRM.
A CRM has data in it and you want to use
lookups in that data. You will probably
give a lookup tool and you will give
access to the resource and it will do
lookups whenever you want. Super fast.
uh this type of architecture can be
built with different degrees of autonomy
from the least autonomous to the most
autonomous and I'll give you a few
examples
less autonomous would be you've
hardcoded the steps so let's say I tell
the travel agent
first identify the intent then um look
up in the database the history of this
customer with us and their preferences
then go to the write API blah blah blah
then go to the I would hardcode the
steps. Okay, that's the least
autonomous. The semi autonomous is I
might hardcode the tools but I'm not
going to hardcode the steps. So, I'm
going to tell the agent um your act like
a travel agent and
um and uh you your task is to help the
person book a travel and these are the
tools that you have accessible to
yourself. And so I'm not hard coding the
steps. I'm just hard coding the tools
that you have access to for yourself. Uh
the more autonomous is the agent decides
the steps and can create the tools. So
that's where you might give actually
access to a code editor to the agent and
the agent might actually be able to ping
any API in the web, perform some web
search. It might even be able to create
some code to display data to the user.
It might even be able to perform some
calculations like, oh, I'm going to
calculate the fastest route to get from
San Francisco to New York. Um, and which
one might be the most appropriate for
what the user is looking for. And then I
want to calculate the distance between
the airport and that hotel versus that
hotel. And I'm going to write code to do
that. So it's actually fully autonomous
from that perspective.
Okay.
So yeah, remember those keywords,
memory, uh prompts, tools, etc.
Now I presented the flight API, but it
does not have to be an API. Uh you
probably have heard the term MCP or
model context protocol that was coined
by anthropic. I I pasted the seminal
article on MCP at the bottom of this
slide. But let me explain in a nutshell
why those things would differ. Um uh in
in the API case um you would actually
teach your LLM to ping an API. So you
would say this is how you ping this API
and this is the data that it will send
you back and um you would have to do
that in a one-off manner. So you would
have to build or sort of give the API
documentation of your flight API, your
booking hotel API, your car rental API
and then you would give tools for your
model to communicate with those APIs. Um
it doesn't scale very well um you know
versus MCP. MCP um it's really about you
know putting a system in the middle sort
of that would make it simpler for your
LLM to communicate with that endpoint.
So for instance um you might you know
have an MCP server and MCP client where
you're trying to communicate with that
travel database or the flight API or MCP
and uh your agent might actually just
communicate with it and say hey what do
you need in order to give me more flight
information and that that agent will
respond by I would like you to tell me
where is the origin flight where is the
destination and what you're looking for
at a high level. This is my requirement.
Okay, let me get back to you with my
requirements. Oh, you forgot to tell me
your budget, whatever. Oh, let me give
you my budget, etc. Um, and uh, it's
it's it's agentto agent communication,
which allows more scalability. You don't
need to hardcode everything. Companies
have displayed their MCPS out there and
you can your agent can communicate with
them and figure out how to get the data
it needs. Does that make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, sorry. like rewriting any help like
it's suffering only changes in the API
rather agent you can rewrite that
>> yes is it not just sh is
>> uh I think it it is ultimately the
question is isn't it chiefing issue
because anyway if an API has to be
updated the MCP has to be updated so
what do you say right yes that that's
correct but at least um it allows the
agent to sort of go back enforce and
figure out what the requirements are.
But at the end of the day, ideally, if
you're a startup, you have some
documentation and automatically have an
agent or an LLM workflow that reads that
documentation and updates the code
accordingly, you know, but I agree it's
not it's not something that is fully
autonomous. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Why is that?
>> Which security specifically?
>> Yeah. So are there security issues with
MCPS?
So think about it this way. MCPS
depending on the data that you get
access to might have different
requirements, lower stake or higher
stake. I'm not an expert at you know the
full range. But it wouldn't surprise me
that um uh you know when you when you
when you expose an MCP to an I think you
would a lot of MCPs have authentication.
So, you know, you might actually need a
code to actually talk to it just like
you would with an API or a key. Um,
yeah, but that's a good question. I'm,
you know, I'm not an expert at the
security of these systems, but, you
know, we can look into it.
Any other questions on what we've seen
with the agentic workflows, APIs, tools,
MCPS, memory? All of that is under
progress. So, even memory is not a
solved problem by any mean. It's pretty
hard actually to get. Yes,
>> you don't need
to confer
to access the API, but technically
engineer uh your way to achieving
something from the API you can do the
same.
>> Exactly. Exactly. Yeah. is is MCP about
efficiency or accessing more data. It's
about efficiency. It's like, you know,
let's say you have a coding agent um and
you know, it has an MCP client and
there's multiple MCP servers that are
exposed out there. Um that agent can
communicate very efficiently with them
and find what it needs. um uh and it's
it's a more efficient process than
actually displaying APIs and the APIs on
that side and how to ping them and what
the protocol is you know but you know
it's not about the data that is being
exposed because ultimately you control
the data that is being exposed
you probably you know depending on how
the MCP is built my guess is you
probably expose yourself to other risks
because your your MCP server can can see
any input pretty much from another LLM
and so it has to be robust. Um
but yeah, super. Uh so let let's look at
an example of a step-by-step uh uh uh
workflow for the travel agent. So let's
say the user says I want to plan a plan
a trip um to Paris from December 15th to
20th um with flights hotels near the FL
tower and then an itinary of must visit
places that's the task to the travel
agent. Step two, the agent plans the
steps. So it says I'm going to find
flights. Use the flight search API uh to
get option for December 15th. Search
hotels, generate recommendation for
places to visit, validate preferences,
um, budget, etc. Book the trip with the
payment processing API. Step three,
that's just the planning by the way.
Step three, execute the plan. Use your
tools, combine the results, and then
proactive user interaction and booking.
It might make a first proposal to the
user and ask the user to validate or
invalidate and then may repeat that
planning and execution process. And then
finally, it might actually update the
memory. It might say, "Oh, I just
learned through this interaction that
the user only likes direct flights. Next
time I I'll only give direct flights."
or I notice users are fine with
threestar hotels or four-star hotels and
in fact they're they don't want to go
above budget or something like that.
Um so that hopefully makes sense by now
on you know how you might do that. My
question for you is uh how would you
know if this works and if you had such a
system running in production how would
you [clears throat] improve it?
Yeah,
>> so that's an example. So let users rate
their experience at the end. Uh that
would be an end to end test, right?
You're looking at the user experience
through the steps and say how good was
it from one to five, let's say. Yeah,
it's a good way. And then if you learn
that a user says one, what how do you
improve the the workflow?
>> Okay, so you would go down a tree and
say, "Okay, you said one uh what what
was your issue?" And then the user says
uh the prices were too high, let's say,
and then you would go back and fix that
specific uh uh tool or prompt or Yeah.
Okay. Any other ideas?
Yeah, good. So that's a good insight.
Separate the LLM related stuff from the
nonLM related stuff. The deterministic
stuff. The deterministic stuff you might
be able to fix it, you know, more
objectively essentially. Yeah, there was
what else?
So, give me an example of an objective
issue that you can notice and how you
would fix it versus a subjective issue.
>> Yeah.
the flight
which is cheaper
directive
that's
>> okay so let's say you say there's the
same flight but one is cheaper than the
other let's say it's objectively worst
and so you can capture that almost
automatically yeah
>> so you could actually build evals that
are objective that are tracked across
your users and you might actually run an
analysis after and see that for the
objective stuff. We noticed that our LLM
AI agentic AI workflow is bad with
pricing. It just doesn't read prices as
well because it always gives a more
expensive option. Yeah, you're perfectly
right. How about the subjective stuff?
>> Yeah.
>> Like do you choose a direct or indirect
flight if the indirect is a little bit
cheaper?
>> Yeah, good one. Do you do you choose a
direct flight or an indirect flight if
the indirect is cheaper but the direct
is more comfortable? Um yeah, that's a
good one actually. Um so how would you
capture that information? Let's say this
is used by thousands of users.
>> Um could you feed something in about us?
>> Uh could you feed something in? Yeah, I
mean you could you could u could you
feed something in uh about the user
preferences? Well, you could you could
build a data set that has some of that
information. So, you build 10 prompts
where the user is asking specifically
for direct is saying that I prefer
direct flights because I care about my
time, let's say. And then you look at
the output and you actually give a good
the example of a good output and you
probably are able to capture the
performance of your agentic workflow on
this specific eval whether does it
prioritize does it understand price
conscious is it price conscious
essentially and comfort conscious
what about the tone let's say let's say
the LLM right now is not very friendly
how would you notice do that and how
would you fix it?
>> Yeah,
>> test user and like run prompts and see
if there's something wrong with
>> Okay, have a test user run the prompt
and see if there's something wrong with
that. Tell me about the last step. How
would you notice that something is
wrong?
So have a couple of
evaluates response and see if it's like
satisfied.
>> Yeah, I agree with your approach. Have
LLM judges that evaluate the response
against a certain rubric of what
politeness look like. So here in this
case you could actually start uh with
error analysis. So you start you have a
thousand users and you know you can pull
up 20 user interaction and read through
it and you might notice at first sight
the LLM seems to be very rude. You know
it's just super super short in its
answers and it's not very helpful. Um
you notice that with your air analysis
manually. Then you go to the next stage.
You actually put eval behind it. you
say, "I'm going to create a set of um a
set of LM judges that are going to look
at the user interaction and are going to
rate how polite it is and I'm going to
give it a rubric. Then what I'm going to
do is I'm going to flip my LLM. Instead
of using GPT4, I'm going to use Grock.
And instead of using Gro, I'm going to
use Lama. And then I'm going to run
those three LLM side by side, give it to
my LLM judges, and then get my
subjective score at the end to say, "Oh,
X model was more polite on average."
Yeah, perfectly right. That's an example
of an EVA that is very specific and
allows you to choose between LM. You
could actually do the same eval across
LM, but fix the LLM, change the prompt.
You actually instead of saying act like
a travel agent, you say act like a
helpful travel agent and then you see
the influence of that word on your eval
with the LLM as judges. Does that make
sense? Okay. Uh super. So let's let's
move forward and do a case study with
eval and then we're we're almost done um
for today. Uh let's say your product
managers manager asks you to build an AI
agent for customer support.
Okay, where do you start? And here is an
example of the user prompt. I need to
change my shipping address for order
blah blah blah. I move to a new address.
So what what do you start if I'm giving
you that project? you know.
>> Yes.
>> So do some research, see benchmarks and
how different models perform at customer
support and then pick a model. That's
what you mean. Yeah. You It's true. You
could do that. What What What else could
you do? Yeah.
>> Okay. Yeah, I like that. Try to
decompose the different tasks that it
will need and try to guess which ones
will be more of a struggle, which ones
should be fuzzy, which one should be
deterministic. Yeah, you're right.
to sit down for like a day or two with a
customer and see how the task
probably task.
>> Yeah, similar to what you said. That's
what I would recommend as well. You say
I would sit down with a customer support
agent for a day or two and I would de
compose the task they're going through.
I will ask them where do they struggle,
how much time it takes. Yes, that's
usually where you want to start with
task decomposition. So let's say we've
done that work and we have this list I'm
simplifying but the customer support
agent human typically would extract info
then look up in the database to retrieve
the customer record then check the
policy you know are we allowed to update
the address or is it a fixed data point
um and then draft the response email and
sends the email okay so we've decomposed
that task
u once you've decomposed that task ask
how do you design your agentic workflow?
>> Yes. each step
which one
which one we're going to use
method or whatever in each task what are
you going to use for resources
>> exactly so to repeat I'm going to you're
going to look at the decomposition of
tasks
get an instinct of what's fuzzy what's
deterministic and then determine which
line is going to be an LLM one shot
which one will require maybe a rag which
one will require a tool, which one will
require memory, which one so you will
start designing that map completely
right that's also what I would recommend
you you might actually uh draft it and
say okay I take the user prompt um and
the first step of my task de composition
was extract information that seems to be
a vanilla LLM you you you can guess that
the vanilla lm would probably be good
enough at extracting the user wants to
change address and this is the order
number and this is the new address. You
probably don't need too much technology
there other than the LLM. Um the next
step it feels like you need a tool
because you're actually going to have to
look up in the database and also update
the address.
So that might be a tool and you might
have to build a custom tool for the LLM
to say let me connect you to that
database or let me give you access to
that resource with an MCP. Yeah.
After that, you probably need an LLM
again to draft the email, but you would
probably paste confirmation. You paste a
confirmation that your address has been
updated from X to Y. And then the LLM
will draft an answer. And of course,
just to not forget, you might need a
tool to send the email. You know, you
might actually need to, you know, post
something to for the email to to go out
and then you'll get the out. Does that
make sense? So, exactly what you
described. [sighs] Okay, now moving to
the next step. Once we have decomposed
our tasks, then we have designed an
agentic workflow around it. It took us
five minutes. In practice, it would take
you more if you're building your startup
on that. You want to make sure your task
de composition is accurate, your thing
is accurate here. And then you can have
a lot of work done on every tool and
optimize it and latency and cost. But
let's say and now we want to know how um
uh if it works, you know, and I'm going
to assume that you have LLM traces. LLM
traces are very important. Actually, if
you're interviewing with an AI startup,
I would recommend you in the interview
process to ask them, do you have LLM
traces? because if they don't have LM
traces, it is pretty hard to debug an
LLM system, you know, because you don't
have visibility on the chain of complex
prompts that were called and where the
bug is and you know, so it's a basic
sort of part of an AI startup stack to
have LLM traces. [laughter] So let's
assume you have traces. How would you
know if your system work? you know, we I
I you know, I I'm going to summarize
some of the things I heard earlier. Um,
you gave us an example of an end to end
metric. You look at the user
satisfaction at the end. Um, you can
also do a component-based approach where
you actually will look at the tool, the
database updates and you will manually
do an error analysis and see, oh, the
tool actually always forgets to update
the email. it just fails at writing, you
know, and I'm gonna fix that. This is
deterministic pretty much. Um or um you
know, when it tries to send the email
and ping the system that is supposed to
send the email, it doesn't send it in
the right format and so it bugs at that
point. Again, you could fix that. Um
draft of the email, the LM doesn't do a
great job. It's not very polite at
drafting the email, you know. So you
could look at component by component and
it's actually easier to debug than to
look at it end to end. You'll probably
do a mix of both. Um another way to look
at it is what is objective versus what
is subjective. So for example an
objective example would be the LLM um
extracted the wrong order ID. You know
the the user said my order ID is X and
the LLM when it actually pasted looked
up in the database it used the wrong
order ID. this is objectively wrong. You
can actually write a Python code that
checks that checks just the alignment
between what the user mentioned and and
what was actually pasted in the database
or for the lookup.
You also have subjective stuff which we
talked about where you probably want to
do either human rating or LLM as judges.
It's very relevant for subjective evals.
[snorts] Um and finally you will find
yourself having quantitative evals and
more qualitative evals. So quantitative
will be percentage of successful address
updates. The latency you could actually
track the latency component based and
see which one is the slowest. Let's say
sending the email is 5 second you know
it's too long let's say you would notice
component based or the full workflow.
And then you will decide where am I
optimizing my latency and how am I going
to do that. And then finally qualitative
you might actually do some error
analysis and look at you know where are
the hallucinations
um where are the tone mismatches
uh you know are the user confused and by
what they're confused you know that
would be more qualitative and typically
it would take more you know white glove
approaches to do that okay so here's
what it could look like I gave you some
examples but you would build evals to
determine objectively, subjectively,
component based, end to- end based and
then quantitatively and qualitatively
where is your LLM failing and where it's
doing well.
Does that give you a sense of the type
of stuff you could do to fix improve
that agentic workflow?
Super. Well, that was our case study on
Evas. We're not going to del deeper into
it, but hopefully it gave you a sense of
the type of stuff you can do with LLM
judges with, you know,
objective, subjective, component-based,
end to end, etc. U last section on
multi- aent workflows.
So you might you might ask uh hey uh why
do we need a multi- aent workflow when
we when the workflow already has
multiple steps already calls the LLM
multiple times already gives them tools
why do we need multiple agents and so
many people are talking about multi-
aent system online it's not even a new
thing frankly I mean multi- aent system
have been around for a long time the the
main advantage of a multi- aent system
is going to be parallelism it's like is
there something that I wish I would run
in parallel
sort of independently but maybe there
are some syncs in the middle but that's
where you want to put a multi- aent
system it's when it's parallel the other
advantage that some companies um have
with multi- aent system is an agent can
be reused. So let's say in a company you
have an agent that's been built for
design. That agent can be used in the
marketing team and it can be used in the
product team, you know, and so now
you're optimizing an agent which has
multiple stakeholders that can
communicate with it and benefit from its
uh performance.
Um actually I'm going to ask you a
question and take a few uh maybe a
minute to think about it. Let's say you
were uh building smart home automation
for your apartment or your home. What
agents would you want to build? Yeah,
write it down and then I'm going to ask
you in in a minute to share some of the
agents that you will build. Also, think
about how you would put a hierarchy
between these agents or how you would
organize them or who should communicate
with who. Okay. Okay. Take a minute for
that.
be creative also because I'm gonna ask
all of your agents and maybe you have an
agent that nobody has thought of.
Okay, let's get started. Who wants to
give me a a set of agents that you would
want for your home smart home? Yes.
So uh the first is like set of agents
that track my movements in the house and
drop information about my house.
Another agent receive that information
and adjust the room temperature
and another
usage of
>> okay so let me repeat you have four
agents I think roughly one that tracks
biometric like you're where are you in
the home where you're moving, how you're
moving, things like that. That sort of
knows your location. The second one um
determines the temperature
of the rooms and has the ability to
change it. The third one tracks energy
efficiency and might be feedback on
energy and energy usage and might be I
don't know maybe it has the control over
the temperature as well. I don't know
actually or the gas or the water might
cut your water at some point
the and then you have an orchestrator
agent. What is exactly the orchestrator
doing?
>> Instructions.
>> Okay. Passes instructions. So is that
the agent that communicates mainly with
the user?
>> Yep.
>> Okay. So if I have I'm coming back home
and I'm saying I want the oven to be
preheated, I communicate with the
orchestrator and then it would funnel to
another agent. Okay, sounds good. Yeah,
so that's an example of a I want to say
a hierarchical um agent multi- aent
system.
Um what else? Any other ideas? What what
would you add to that? Yeah.
>> minimal action that you can do. Imagine
entering a room or just entering a
computer or just opening the minimum
kind of action. you have like lot of
agent per
[clears throat]
and then depending on who who is it and
all the contact you have
>> oh I like that that's a really good one
so let me summarize you have a security
agent that determines if you can enter
or not and when you enter it understands
who you are and then it gives you
certain sets of permissions that might
be different depending of if you're a
parent or a or you know you might have
access to certain cars and not others or
the kid cannot open the fridge or I
don't know like something like that.
Yeah. Or okay. I like that. That's a
good one. Yeah. And it does feel like
it's a complex enough workflow where you
want a specific workflow tied to that. I
I agree. [snorts]
>> What What else?
>> Yes. Continuing on the ambient stuff,
you can get more complicated. So energy
savings with
keeps open
as well
from the grocery store understand what's
in your fridge or not.
who are out to.
>> Well, that's really good actually. So,
you mentioned two of them. One is maybe
an agent that has access to external
APIs that can understand the weather out
there, the wind, the sun, and then has
control over certain devices at home,
temperature, blinds, things like that,
and also understands your preferences
for it. that does feel like it's a good
use case because you could give that to
the orchestrator but it might lose
itself because it's doing too much. So
you probably and also these problems are
tied together like temperature outdoor
with the weather API might influence the
temperature inside how you want it etc.
And then the second one which I also
like is you might have an agent that
looks at your fridge and what's inside
and it might actually have access to the
camera in the fridge for example. Um and
know your preferences and also has
access to the e-commerce API to order
Amazon groceries ahead of time. Um I
agree and maybe the orchestrator will be
the communication line with the user but
it might communicate with that agent um
in order to get it done. Uh yeah I like
those. So those are all uh really good
examples here. Here is the list I had um
up there. So climate control, lighting,
security, energy management,
entertainment, notification agent,
alerts about the system updates, energy
saving and orchestrator. So all of them
you mentioned actually. Um and then we
didn't talk about the different
interaction patterns, but you do have
different ways to organize a multi- aent
system. flat hierarchical. It sounds
like this would be hierarchical. I
agree. And the reason is UIUX is I would
rather have to only talk to the
orchestrator rather than have to go to a
specialized application to do something
like it feels like the orchestrator
could be responsible for that. And so I
agree I would probably go for a
hierarchical setup here. But maybe you
might act also add some connections
between other agents like in the flat
system where it's all to all for example
uh with climate control and energy if
you want to connect those two. You might
actually allow them to speak with each
other. When you allow agents to speak
with each other it is basically an MCB
protocol by the way. So you treat the
agent like a tool exactly like a tool.
Here is how you interact with this
agent. Here is what it can tell you.
Here is what it needs from you
essentially.
Okay, super. And then without going into
the details, there are advantages to
multi- aent workflows versus, you know,
single agents such as debugging. It's
easier to special debug a specialized
agent and to be debug an entire system.
Parallelization as well. It's easier to
have things run in parallel. Um, and you
can earn time. Um, you know, there are
some advantages to doing that. And I
leave you with this slide if you want to
go deeper. Super. So we've learned so
many techniques to optimize LLMs from
prompts to chains to finetuning
retrieval um and to multi- aent system
as well. And then just to end on um a
couple of trends I want you to watch. Uh
I think next week is Thanksgiving. Is
that it? Is Thanksgiving break? No, the
week after. Okay. Well, ahead of the
Thanksgiving break. So if you're
traveling, you can think about these
things. Um what's next is in AI, I
wanted to call out a couple of trends.
Um so Elas discover one of the OGs of uh
you know LLM's um and you know OpenAI
co-ounder um raised that question about
are we plateauing or not? You know the
question of are we going to see in the
coming years LLM sort of not improve as
fast as we've seen in the past. It's
been the feeling in the community
probably that you know the last version
of GPT um did not bring the level of
performance that people were expecting
although it did make it so much easier
to use for consumers because you don't
need to interact with different models
it's all under the same hood so it seems
that it's progressing um but the plateau
is is unclear the the way I would think
about it is um
the LLM scaling laws tell us that if we
continue to improve compute and energy
then LM should continue to improve but
at some point it's going to plateau so
what's going to take us to the next step
and it's probably architecture search
still a lot of LLM even if we don't
understand what's under the hood are
probably transformer based today but we
know that the human brain does not
operate the same way there's just
certain things that we do that are much
more efficient much faster we don't need
as much data so theoretically we have so
much to learn in terms of architecture
search that we haven't figured out. It's
not a surprise that you see those labs
hire so many engineers because it is
possible that in the next few years
you're going to have thousands of
engineers trying to figure out the
different engineering hacks and tactics
and architectural searches that are
going to lead to better models and one
of them suddenly will find the next
transformer and it will reduce by 10x
the need for compute and the need for
energy. Um, you know, it's sort of if
you've read Isak Azimov's u foundation
series um individuals can have an
amazing impact on the future because of
their decisions. You know, whoever
discovered transformers had a tremendous
impact on the direction of AI. I think
we're going to see more of that in the
coming years where some group of
researcher that is iterating fast might
discover certain things that would
suddenly unlock that plateau and take us
to the next step and it's going to
continue to improve like that. And so it
doesn't surprise me that there's so many
companies hiring engineers right now to
figure out those hacks and those those
techniques. Um the other set of gains
that we might see is from multimodality.
So the way to think about it is we've
we've we've had LLM first text based and
then we've added imaging and today you
know models are very good at images.
They're very good at text. Turns out
that being good at images and being good
at text makes the whole model better. So
the fact that you're good at
understanding a cat image makes you
better at text as well for a cat. Now
you add another modality like audio or
video, the whole system gets better. So
you're better at writing about a cat if
you know what a cat sounds like if you
can look at a cat on an image as well.
Does that make sense? So we see gains
that are translated from one modality to
another. And that might lead in the
pinnacle of robotics where all these
modalities come together and suddenly
the robot is better at running away from
a cat because it understands what a cat
is, how it sounds like, what it looks
like, etc. That make sense? Um, the
other one is the multiple methods
working in harmony. In the Tuesday
lectures, we've seen supervised
learning, unsupervised learning,
self-supervised learning, reinforcement
learning, quality engineering, rags,
etc. If you look at um how babies learn
um it is probably a mix of those
different approaches like a baby um
might have some metalarning meaning you
know it has some survival instinct that
is in the encoded in the DNA most likely
um and that's like the baby's
pre-training if you will on top of that
uh the mom or the dad um is pointing at
stuff and saying bad good bad good good
supervised learning on top of that the
baby's falling on the ground and getting
hurt and that's a reward signal for
reinforcement learning. On top of that,
the baby's observing other people doing
stuff or other babies, you know, doing
stuff, unsupervised learning. You see
what I mean? It's we're probably a mix
of all these methods and um and I think
that's where the trend is going is where
those methods that you've seen in CS230
come together in order to build an AI
system that learns fast, is low latency,
is cheap, energy efficient, and makes
the most out of all of these methods.
Um, finally, and this is especially true
at Stanford, um, you have research going
on that you would consider human centric
and some research that is nonhuman
centric. By humancentric, I should say
human approaches that are modeled after
the brain and approaches that are not
modeled after humans because it turns
out that the human body is very
limiting. And so if you actually only do
research on what the human brain looks
like, you're probably missing out on
compute and energy and stuff like that
that you can optimize even beyond
neuronal connections in the brain. But
you still can learn a lot from the human
brain. And that's why there are
professors that are running labs right
now that try to understand how does back
propagation work for humans. And in
fact, it's probably that we don't have
back propagation. We don't use back
propagation. We only do forward
propagation, let's say. So this type of
stuff is interesting research that I
would encourage you to read if you're
curious about the direction of of AI. Um
and then finally um one thing that's
going to be pretty clear I call it all
the time but it's the velocity at which
things are moving. You're noticing part
of the reason we're we're giving you a
breath in CS230 is because these methods
are changing so fast. So I don't want to
bother going and teaching you the number
17 methods on rag that optimizes the rag
because in two years you're not going to
need it, you know. So I would rather you
think about what is the breadth of
things you want to understand and when
you need it you are sprinting and
learning the exact thing you need faster
because the half-life of ski is so low
you know you want to come out of the
class with a good breath and then have
the ability to go deep whenever you need
after the class and so that's sort of
how that class is designed as well. Um
yeah that's it for today. So thank you
um thank you for participating.